TSVETAN IVANOV

Sofia, Bulgaria / +359 88 5532644 tsvetan.ivanov1@gmail.com/ LinkedIn

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Software Engineer with over 4 years of experience in all aspects of the software development life cycle including gathering requirements, writing specifications, designing, coding, integration, testing and maintenance. Highly motivated to provide innovative software solutions to meet goals and satisfy needs of an organization.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING SKILLS

- Solutions Engineering, Testing & Optimization
- Service-Oriented Architecture (SOA)
- Web Development

- Agile software development
- Single-Page Applications
- Object-Oriented Methodologies

Professional Experience

Software Developer Contractor at Kingfield Corporation June 2017 – Present

Participated in the design and implementation of a system for standardized communication between firms in the cloud. Utilized technologies include Azure Service Fabric, Outlook add-ons, Microservices architecture. Created ASP.NET Core based Web Application for organization/team management and issues resolution using standardized industry messages.

Software Developer at Soft2Run April 2016 – June 2017

Ruukki Construction Link

Targets: Renew 20+ websites, with two brands

Involved in Software development life cycle (SDLC) of the application from design phase to the implementation phase, testing, Deployment and maintenance phase. Participated in the daily stand up SCRUM agile meetings as part of the AGILE process for reporting the day to day developments of the work done. Utilized technologies, methodologies and tools include Web Renewal, Continuous development, Sitefinity, Eloqua, Salesforce, ASP.NET, HAProxy, Scrum, JIRA, Confluence, Git, CCNet, Continuous Integration, Continuous Deployment, AWS, AWS Lambda, PDF Generation, Docraptor, Visual Testing (Wraith)

Lindström Management Portal

Implemented all the remaining functionalities required by the clients to finish their intranet Sitefinity project. Utilized technologies, methodologies and tools include Sitefinity, Elasticsearch, Scrum, JIRA, Confluence, ASP.NET MVC, React, Git, Continuous Integration, Continuous Deployment, Microsoft Azure, Visual Studio Online.

Layer2 Solutions Link

Targets: Transition the old Layer 2 SharePoint site to Sitefinity and redesign it

Implement all the backend functionalities with Sitefinity MVC widgets. Provide expertise and educate Layer 2 developers how to get the most out of Sitefinity. Utilized technologies, methodologies and tools include Elasticsearch, Scrum, JIRA, Confluence, ASP.NET MVC, React, Git, Continuous Integration, Continuous Deployment, Microsoft Azure, Visual Studio Online.

Software Developer at Title X Technology March 2014 – April 2016

Created multiple Sitefinity, ASP.NET MVC and ASP.NET Web API including:

Bizu Link

Implementation of functionality for the backend of the mobile applications. And creation of the web based admin portal for the stores. Utilized technologies, methodologies and tools include ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web API, HTML, CSS, AngularJs.

Social achievement Link

Implementation of Sitefinity based web application for keeping track of all the students and organizations which are part of the project for helping kids to receive a proper education. Participated in many sessions with the clients to extract all the requirements for the project. Utilized technologies, methodologies and tools include Sitefinity, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, jQuery

Technology Summary		
C# ASP.NET Core ASP.NET Web Forms Sitefinity T-SQL Git TFS JavaScript ReactJS	HTML CS, MS SQL Server jQuery Entity Framework Azure AWS TypeScript Elasticsearch	Angular MongoDB LINQ Continuous Integration Continuous Deployment JIRA Confluence Bootstrap
Hobbies		
• Tennis	• Travelling	• Cooking

EDUCATION

BS in Computer Science / SOFIA UNIVERSITY ST. KL. OHRIDSKI

Certifications: